squiby.net 2017-12-11

# 

#### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Squiby collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users.

**Squiby respects their members and wishes to satisfy everyone's expectations.**

## Web browser cookies

Squiby may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. Members' web browser places cookies on their browser/hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Members may choose to disclose cookie information in their browser settings, however it may result in loosing information, often logouts or upon browsing Squiby, some features may not function properly.

#### **How the data-collected cookies are used**

• _Your stored information is used so the site may display features correctly. This will prevent logouts, loss of info,  and errors if you choose to share information._

• _Your stored information and data helps us to improve the site on how members use features and resources on Squiby. This allows us to keep track of our features, and possibly enchance them, and allow us to choose what and whatnot features & resources we should keep or get ridden of!_

• _Your stored information may also be important as to sending e-mails/messages that pertain to your requests._

• _May help us with banned or restricted users and bots who MAY create multiple accounts to break site rules._

## _What information is collected by our database?_

  * Browser information is recorded which contains name and version of the web browser.

  * IP (Internet Protocol) address may be recorded to identify the user.

  * Cookie/s to collect login information is tracked.

  * Advertisers, like Google may track the cookies and their policy can be reviewed at their websites.

  * The account username and email address of the users are recorded.

  * The information you provide to describe yourself is public and you can hide it anytime.

  * Your address and location in your profile is not shared. Only city/country displayed in your profile can be seen by other users.

  * We will record time and login attempts for your security

  * Posts and topics created on the forum by your account are public unless you created a closed group.

  * Private messages sent from your account will not be seen by users other than the recipients.

  * No credit cards or any transaction information done through the squiby will be stored or recorded by squiby website. Transactions done through paypal will be governed by their terms which can be read at their website.

## How do we use this collected information?

  * IP address and browser information is used to identify the correct user, geographic region and the browser versions.

  * Cookies are recorded by server to provide quick access to accurate and up to date web content.

  * Account information is used to secure access to your account and allow username and password change and reset.

  * The email associated with the account is only used for correspondence and will not be shared with third party.

  * For the account security login attemps will be recorded.

  * Your adoptable collection, creations, blogs and other material will not be shared with any third party by squiby website.

  * The Squiby Website will not be responsible for any information (private or public) shared or distributed by other users on any media or social network.

  * The Squiby administrators will take appropriate action including permanent ban if a breach of this policy is reported. Please also see Rules and terms of use for this website.

  * Google adsense privacy policy can be reviewed at their website.

## Who has access to this information?

Who has access to the information?

  * Only administrators including developer of the website will have access to the recorded information.

  * For the sake of security and integrity of site we reserve the right to disclose information (including personal information) to authorities to prevent threats and misuse of our website. How we use this information?

  * IP address and browser information is used to identify the correct user, geographic region and the browser versions.

  * Cookies are recorded by server to provide quick access to accurate and up to date web content.

  * Account information is used to secure access to your account and allow username and password change and reset.

  * The email associated with the account is only used for correspondence and will not be shared with third party.

  * For the account security login attemps will be recorded.

  * Your adoptable collection, creations, blogs and other material will not be shared with any third party by squiby website.

  * The Squiby Website will not be responsible for any information (private or public) shared or distributed by other users on any media or social network.

  * The Squiby administrators will take appropriate action including permanent ban if a breach of this policy is reported. Please also see Rules and terms of use for this website.

  * Google adsense privacy policy can be reviewed at their website.

  * We are committed to enforce our site rules, to protect or defend our rights and property or ensure the safety and security of our users.

  * If such malicious activity is noticed we are legally required to provide all information to appropriate regulatory authorities.

## Keeping you protected!

We **_DO NOT_** disclose any personal information or data to _**_ANYONE_**_. These records are  _ _ **ONLY**__  kept between the Squiby Team.

• We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

• We do not release, sell, trade, or rent our members' personal identification information to others (including affiliates and advertisers).  

• **In Compliance with the COPPA** (Children's online privacy protection Act) Our website is for all ages, and we are very protective of the younger ones on Squiby because they are important. Therefore, we do not allow adult-content, suspicious links, or any other dangerous content that target or aim to attract our younger member base. We wish to keep Squiby PG-13 and under! Therefore, we also keep our info boxes optional, users may fill them out if they wish to or not since these boxes record information such as City, State & Country. We do not disclose info on specific locations of users.

  * Our database is protected by firewalls and secure access controls. Offsite backups are encrypted and protected by firewalls and antivirus.

However, we still wish to acknowledge younger ones that we do collect cookie information from younger members too, and that they should even seek parental permissions to use Squiby.  **NO** part of our website is _**specifically**_ set to attract those 13 and younger. **Squiby is for all ages.  **And, we do encourage younger ones to be careful with releasing private and personal info online; to not mention them at **all**. 

## In case of changes in our Privacy Policy...

Squiby has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time to ensure our members' privacy. Upon updating, it will be announced and you may recieve an e-mail to acknowledge the update of our Privacy Policy. **  _Is it very imporant. We wish for our members to stay informed of our Policy, and to actually read it._**

And so by using our website, you hereby acknowledge; completely understand your acceptance of this policy and use of Squiby. If you do not agree to this policy, we suggest not to continue using Squiby. You can also submit ideas and questions about our Policy to the Squiby Team.

##### This Policy is currently up-to-date as of 5/21/2017.
